Finding Aid for the Horace Tapscott Papers PASC-M.0237
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sound Recordings, Series 1.
  - Assorted Identified Sound Recordings, Subseries 1.
    - Widney H.S. (24th and Gramercy), 12/13/1970; 2 of 2 (Box 21, Folder 15)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Guido, tenor sax; Hassan, tenor sax; Semadi, bass; Fritz Wise, drums
      Compositions: My Reverie (or Revere), Blues
    - Sherman McKinney Group, 12/14/1970; 1 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Linda Hill, vocal
      Compositions: Malik's Haj (ecpt), Fo Fats, Springtime in Africa (Duke), Malik's Haj, Effendi (El Malik)
    - Sherman McKinney Group, 12/14/1970; 2 of 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Malik's Haj, Reading of Slaves, Little Niles
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney H.S., 1970 December 20; 1 of 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      The Community Cultural Arkestra. Compositions: Equinox.
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney H.S., 1970 December 20; 2 of 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      The Community Cultural Arkestra. Compositions: drums solo -- Fatisha / Will Connell.
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney H.S., 1970 December 20; 3 of 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Free Form Quintet
      Personnel: Lino, piano; Doug, cornet and french horn; Will, alto sax & flute; Yusef, bass; Tylan, percussion. Compositions: Sentimental Mood.
    - D.T.S. Concerts, 01/06/1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Compositions: Star of the Seas, Woman, The Grip, Warriors All, Effie
    - Study Tape Series, 01/07/1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Lino's Pad, Thoughts, (For) J.O.B., St. Michael
    - Cal State LA, 1971 January 13 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      Poets of UGMAA. Personnel: Luther Keyes - Nigguh, I Love You; Ojenke - Call Me Crazy. The Arkestra. Compositions: Freedom's Sweet -- Effie.
    - P.A.S.L.A., 01/17/1971; 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      The ARK
      Compositions: Dem Folks, Little Africa, Master's at Work
    - P.A.S.L.A, 01/17/1971; 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      The Arkestra. Compositions: Gone, Say it Over and Over Again, Celia
    - Widney High School, 02/14/1971; 1 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute; Robert Roy, flute; Chico R, flute; Black Arthur; Will C; Cerion; Ray S; Guido S, baritone; Butch; Troy Brown, trumpet and drums; Lester; David B; Everett; Jimmy Hoskins, drums; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Willie Samprite, trumpet; David Straughter, drums
      Compositions: Equinox, Effendi, Ballad for Samuel, Lino's Pad
    - Widney High School, 02/14/1971; 2 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Lino's Pad, Little A's Chant, Sketches of Drunken Mary, Effi
    - Widney High School, 02/14/1971; 3 of 3 (Box 25, Folder 8)
      Compositions: Lino's Pad (cont)
    - Campbell Hall, 1971 February 19 (Box 25, Folder 9)
      Compositions: Solo Piano - Pige's Piano.
      Community Cultural Arkestra plus The Voices of UGMAA.
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney H.S., 1971 February 21; 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 10)
      The Arkestra
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Cerion; Nate; Greg Tell; Jimmy Hoskins; Everett; David S (4 drummers); Lester; Ernest S; Ray S; Guido; Cojoe. Compositions: Effendi -- Effie -- Fo' Fats -- Ballad for Samuel -- Lino's Pad.
    - Concert in Black Music at Widney H.S., 02/21/1971; 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 11)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Cerion; Nate; Greg Tell; Jimmy Hoskins; Everett; David S (4 drummers); Lester; Ernest S; Ray S; Guido; Cojoe
      Compositions: Effendi, Effi, Fo' Fats, Ballad for Samuel, Lino's Pad
    - Cal State, 1971 March 6 (Box 25, Folder 12)
      Compositions: Effendi.
    - The Arkestra at Widney H.S., 1971 March 7; 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 13)
      Compositions include: Carnival -- Inkata -- Drunken Mary.
      Personnel includes: Horace Tapscott, piano; Ernest Straughter, flute, oboe; Robert Roy, flute; Butch; Troy, trumpet; Will, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Cerion; Ray S; Guido S, baritone sax; Lester; Robert Sims, baritone sax; David B; Walter S; Everet; Cojoe, congas
    - The Arkestra at Widney H.S., 03/07/1971; 2 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 14)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; Ernest S, flute, oboe; Robert Roy, flute; Butch; Troy, trumpet; Will, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Cerion; Ray S; Guido S, baritone sax; Lester; Robert Sims, baritone sax; David B; Walter S; Everet; Cojoe, congas
      Compositions: Little A's Chant, Effendi, Luther Keyes - "I Love You", Ballad for Samuel Effi
    - The ARK at Widney and UGMAAS, 03/14/1971; 1 of 2 (Box 25, Folder 15)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute, oboe; Robert Roy, flute; Butch; Troy, trumpet; Will, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Cerion; Ray S; Guido S, baritone sax; Lester; Robert Sims, baritone sax; David B; Walter S; Everett; Cojoe, congas
      Compositions: Prance Dance, Inkata, Haunted, Theme for Rhea, Effi, Lush Life
    - [Selections], 1971 March 14 (Box 25, Folder 16)
      Compositions: Impressions -- Delugee' -- All Blues.
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest Straughter, flute, oboe; Robert Roy, flute; Butch; Troy, trumpet; Will, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Cerion; Ray S; Guido Sinclair, baritone sax; Lester Robertson; Robert Sims, baritone sax; David Bryant; Walter S; Everett Brown, Jr.; Cojoe, congas. Bob Davis Septet. Personnel: Bob Davis, alto sax; Eddie Liddie, trumpet, flugelhorn; Larry M. Ali, tenor sax; Nate Morgan, piano; Ron Dodey, bass; Yusef Mumin, bass; Harold Lacy, drums. Tape 2 of 2.
    - Quintet Plus at Widney H.S., 03/21/1971 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Ernest S, flute; Lester; Robert Roy, flute; Will C; Black Arthur; Cerion; Ray S; Guido; Bari; Willie L, trumpet; Troy Brown, trumpet; Butch, cornet; David B; Everett; David Straughter, drums; Cojoe, congas
      Compositions: Equinox, Lester, Prance Dance, Listen My Children
    - KUSC FM Radio Broadcast, 03/28/1971; 1 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      Compositions: The Giant Is Awakened, Goldpower
    - KUSC FM Radio Broadcast, 03/28/1971; 2 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - KUSC FM Radio Broadcast, 03/28/1971; 3 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - KUSC FM RADIO Broadcast, 03/28/1971; 4 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - KUSC FM Radio Broadcast, 03/28/1971; 5 of 5 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Malcom X Week at Riverside City College, 05/22/1971 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      Future Present Tense UGMAA
      Personnel: Ron Wilson, piano; Paul Wright, bass; John Blue, drums; Ray S, tenor sax
      Compositions: E.P., Mankind Is One, Hot Rotten Collard Greens, Paul Chant, Passion and Compassion
    - The Art at RCC Landers Auditorium, George Quant, M.C., 05/22/1971 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Linda Hill, vocal; Ernest S, flute; Robert Toy, flute; Black Arthur; Will C; Cerion; Ray S; Hassan, tenor sax; W. Samprite, trumpet; David B; David Straughter, drums; Everett; Cojoe, congas; Luther Keyes, poet; Tobie Hopkins, poet (W/Watts Writers Wshop- Lived in Riverside)
      Compositions: Little A's Chant (with vocals by Linda Hill), Prance Dance, Lift Up Your Voice, poets
    - Live at Joyce's HOuse (Nyja's mom), 05/28/1971; 1 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott, piano; David B, bass
      Compositions: Sugar Corn for Grace, Sonny's Dream
    - Live at Joyce's House (Nyja's mom), 05/28/1971; 2 of 2 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      Compositions: The Gathering, Evenings Last Sun Rays, Spellbound, Fatitia
    - Black Experience Class at Riverside City College (R.C.C.), 1971 June (Box 27, Folder 12)
      Instructor: Horace Tapscott.
    - Black Experience Class at Riverside City College (R.C.C.), 1971 June (Box 74, Folder 1)
      Horace Tapscott, instructor. Tape 1 of 2.
    - Black Experience Class at Riverside City College (R.C.C.), 1971 June (Box 74, Folder 2)
      Horace Tapscott, instructor. Tape 2 of 2.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1971 June 6 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      Compositions: Little A's Chant -- Sonata No. 1, Theme/Variations -- Allegro con Blvd -- Engrams.
      Personnel: Natalie Hinderas, artist.
    - Music by Black Composers, 06/29/1971 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      Personnel: Natalie Hinderas, piano
      Compositions: Dark Horsemen, Summer Land, Radiant Pinnacle, At a Certain Church, Ring Game, Visitor form Town, In the Bottoms Suite (HT) - A. Prelude, B. His Song, C. Honey, D. Barcarolle, E. Dance (Juba), Easter Mopnday Swaggers, Dark Tree, Niger's Theme, On Time
    - Concert in Blamus, 07/25/1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      The Ark-ho-ta at Widney
      The Arkestra and Voice
      Vocals: Chanima, Isis, Katu, Aminifu, Lino, Chaga (Ali Jihad)
      Compositions: Effendi, Inkata, Carnival, Flight 17
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney High School, 1971 August 8 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark at Widney, 1971 August 22; 1 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      Compositions: L.P. -- Giant Steps -- Not At All -- Freedom's Sweet -- David's Chant.
      Personnel: Ernest Straughter, flute; Will Connell, alto sax; Black Arthur, alto sax; Walter Graham, trumpet; Willie Samprite, trumpet; Cerion Middeton III, tenor sax; Ray Straughter, tenor sax; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; David Straughter, drums; Robert Miranda, bass; Walter Savage, bass.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark at Widney, 1971 August 22; 2 of 2 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      Compositions: Freedom's Sweet -- Horace Speaks -- The Whistler Calls -- Ballad for Samuel -- Child of Love -- Little Africa -- Effie / Stanley Cowell -- Chant -- Oleo.
    - Flight Seventeen, 08/29/1971 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      The Arkestra at Widney High School
    - Equinox, 08/29/1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      Composition: Equinox
    - Thoughts of Dar es Salaam, 08/29/1971 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      Composition: Thoughts of Dar es Salaam
    - Watts Writers Workshop, 09/19/1971; 1 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      PAPA at Widney High School
      Compositions: Children, Oh Tananya, Black Anthem, Effi
      Watts Writers Workshop
      Cmpositions: Effendi, Dem Folks, Why Don't You Listen
    - Flight 17, 09/19/1971; 2 of 2 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      Compositions: Flight 17, Dar es Salaam
    - Why Don't You Listen, 10/03/1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      The Ark at Widney High School
      Personnel: Ernest; R. Roy; Will; Black; Cerion; Ray; Azar, baritone; Douglas; Willie L.; Walter G.; Lester, trombone; David, bass; Richard Herrera; Everett, percussion; Fritz Wise; CoJoe, congas; Nate, piano; Horace, piano and conductor Compositions: Why Don't You Listen, Little A's Chant, Little Africa, The Black Antham, Effie
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at PALSA and the Voices of UGMAA, 1971 November 7 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      Compositions: Dem Folks -- Little Africa -- Masters at Work.
      Personnel includes: Linda Hill, vocals; Sister Chanima, vocals; Lester, trombone; Nate Morgan, piano.
    - Widney Series, 11/10/1971 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      Personnel: Ernest Straughter, flute; David Bryant, bass violin; Nate Morgan, piano; Black Arthur, alto and soprano sax; Everett Browne, percussion; Lil'David Straughter, percussion; Lester Roberson, trombone; Robert Roy, flute; Ray Straughter, tenor sax; Walter Graham, trumpet; Butch Morris, trumpet; Azar Laurence, baritone sax; Cerion Middleton III, tenor sax; Ernest CoJoe, congas, Fritz Wise, percussion, Horace Tapscott, conductor and piano
      Voice of UGMAA: Linda Hill, Sister Aminifu (Frances Lark), Ruth Holman, Bro. Ghaga (Charles Galloway)
      Compositions: L.T.T., Fo' Fats, Effendi, I Felt Spring, Dem' Folk, O'Tananya, Little Africa, Equinox, Black Woman, E.P., Lift Every Voice
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra, 1971 November 10 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      Theme Music "Effie" by Stanley Cowell, Linda Hill Lyrics.
      Personnel: Ernest Straughter, Flute; David Bryant, Bass Violin; Nate Morgan, Piano; Black Arthur, alto and soprano saxophones; Everett Brown, Jr., Percussion; Lil David Straughter, percussion; Robert Roy, flute; Ray Straughter, tenor sax; Walter Graham, trumpet; Butch Morris, trumpet; Azar Laurence, baritone sax; Cerion Middleton III, tenor Sax; Ernest Cojoe, congas; Fritz Wise, percussion. Voice of UGMAA; Miss Linda Hill; Sister Aminizo; AKA. - Frances Lark; Ruth Holman; Bro. Chaga.- AKA. Charles Galloway. John Stitt, community speaker; Horace Tapscott, pianist and conductor.
    - Tribute to Sam Brown, 11/14/1971 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      PAPA in Concert and Voices of UGMAA
      Compositions: Ballad for Samuel, Motherless Child, The Funeral, Effenci, Black Anthem
    - The Ark at Pasla: Tribute to Sam Brown, 11/14/1971 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      Compositions: Ballad For Samuel; Motherless child; The Funeral; Effendi; Black Anthem.
    - PAPQ and Voices of UGMAA at Widney, 12/12/1971 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      Personnel: Horace Tapscott; Black ARthur, alto and soprano; Lester Robertson; RIchard Herrera, bass; E.B., percussion; Cojoe
      Voices: Aminifu, Chaga, R. Holman, Linda
      Compositions: Dem Folks, Giant Is Awakened, Motherless Child, Not At All
    - The Pan African Peoples Quintet And Voices of UGMAA, 12/12/1971 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      At Widney: Personnel: Horace Tapscott; black Arthur, alto and Sopr., Lester Robertson, Richard Herrera, bass; E.B. perc.; Cojoe; Voices: Aminifu, Chaga, R. Holman, Linda.
      Compositions: Dem Folks, Giant is Awakened, Motherless Child, Not at All.
    - First Quintet From UGMAA, 12/12/1971 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      personnel: Black Arthur, alto sax; lester Robertson, trombone; Richard Herrera, bass Violin; Everett brwon Jr., drums; Horace Tapscott, piano; Sister Linda Hill, Aminifu; Brother chaga; Ernest Cojoe, congas. Composition: The Giant is Awakened
    - UGMAA, 12/16/1971 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      Compositions. Side one: Japan, Theme X, Hello to the Wind, Now, Night Dreamer, related to what, Blackis, Black Peoples, Sun ship, Tranquility, Little Poem, Malcom, Today, slow Change, Evolution, the sun, Peace, Let the Rain Fall, Astral traveling, the ankia of Amen-RA, Pastoral.
      Side two: Infant Eyes, Come Rain or Come Shine, Darn that dream, There is no greater love, Effendi, Bags Groove, Um Um Um, Minor Blues, My Funny Valentine, Bouquet, The Prophet, Call me by my richful, Oh ALLAH, dearly beloved, Echoes, Japan, Bye, Kush.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), the ARK at Widney, December 26, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      part 2
    - At Widney, December 26, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      duplicate
    - The Ark at Widney High School 12/26/1971, 1971 December 26; pasc-m_0237_030_006a; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 audiotape; Duration: 1:01:52) (Box 30, Case 6)
      Transcribed from container: "The Ark - PAPA - At Widney / Concert in Bla'mus / C.S. 122671 YOUS / Part 1 'Two Sides'" Side 2: "The Creator... (Pt. II) / 2. Motherless Child (Negro Spiritual) / Luther Keyes - Poem - On the Spot... / 3. Little A's Chant (Herbert Baker) / Flight 17 (Herbert Baker) / Little A's Chant (Herbert Baker) / Horace Speaks - Introduces Ark - ark eyes - next tune..." Also noted: "Part 2: Little Africa (cont'd ->"
    - The Ark at Widney High School 12/26/1971, 1971 December 26; pasc-m_0237_030_006b; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:58:58) (Box 30, Case 6)
      Transcribed from container: "The Ark - PAPA - At Widney / Concert in Bla'mus / C.S. 122671 YOUS / Part 1 'Two Sides'" Side 1: "1. Isle of Celia (H.K.T.) 2. Softly As In A Morning Sunrise ( ) 3. Straight Street (J. Coltrane) 4. Equinox (J. Coltrane) 5. The Creator Has A Master Plan (Pt. 1) (P. Saunders - L. Thomas)"
    - Elaine Brown, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - For My People, 1972; pasc-m_0237_030_001; Tapscott, Horace; 1 sound recordings (1 1/4 inch audiotape; Duration: 0:14:12) (Box 30, Case 1)
      Transcribed from container: Gilmore "Instrumental" William Marshall. Thoughts of Dar Es Salaam. Tananya- Linda Hill and others vocal. Recorded Mick Stevenson's Studio 1972.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney, January 9, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      Compositions include: In a Sentimental Mood -- Niger's Theme -- Little A's Chant -- Lush Life -- Free Lester / Will C. -- Eye of the Storm / Bobby Bradford -- Drunken Mary -- Creator Has A Master Plan -- Sunrise Sunset (From "fiddler on the Roof" maybe Linda would sing sometimes) -- Black National Anthem -- Effie.
    - UCR: David Bryant, Black Musician, Sping 1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), The ARK at Widney, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Compositions: In a Sentimental Mood / D. Ellington -- Niger's Theme / Horace Tapscott -- Littlea's Chant / Herbert T.Baxer -- Lush life / Billy Strayhorn.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), February 3, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      Horace Tapscott: instructor. Subject: David Bryant, Black Musician.
    - Pan Afrikan Quintet at Riverside, February 9, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Personnel: David B., Everett B., Black Arthur, alto and sopr., Lester R., Horace Tapscott, Linda, voice. Compositions: Motherless Child -- Fo Fats / Arthur Blythe -- Equinox -- Dem Folks -- Little Africa -- Black Anthem -- Effie.
    - Pan Afrikan Quintet plus One at Riverside, 1972 February 9 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      Wednesday Night. Compositions: Motherless child -- Fo Fats / Arthur Blythe -- Equinox -- Dem Folks -- Little Africa -- Black Anthem -- Effie.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Quintet plus one at Riverside, February 9,1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      Wednesday Night
      Personnel: David B., Everett B., Black Arthur, alto and sopra, Lester R., Horace Tapscott, Linda, voice
      Compositions: Motherless Child, Fo Fats, (Arthur Blythe), Equinox, Dem Folks, Little Africa, Black Anthem, Effi
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney, February 20, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      Compositions include: Morning in Riverside -- Blues -- Chant.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), Ark at Widney, 1972 February 20 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      Compositions: Morning in Riverside (written by one of Ark) -- Blues -- Chant.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 March 7 (Box 72)
      Plight of the Black Artist. Horace Tapscott, instructor.
    - UGNMAA Arkives LP's, including: Coltrane in Europe with Eric Dolphy, 1972 March 16 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: My Favorite Things -- Impressions -- Naima -- All My Yesterdays -- Utopia -- Malcolm X -- Mode TO John -- Man From Tanganyika -- Smitty's Place -- Vision -- African Village -- Peresina -- Hum-Allah-Hum-Allah-Hum-Allah.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, 1972 March 26 (Box 72)
      Composition: Deon.
    - Pan Afrikan People's Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), ARK at Widney, Part I, 1972 March 26 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Deon -- Calvary.
    - Pan Afrikan People's Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), ARK at Widney, Part II, 1972 March 26 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Calvary (part 2) -- Little Africa / Linda Hill.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.) + Quintet, Recorded for KUSC FM, 1972 March 29 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Inspirations of Silence / Ernest Straughter -- Focus On Sanity / Ornette Coleman.
      Personnel includes: Larry Gales, cello; David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown, Jr., drums; Black Arthur, alto saxophone; Horace Tapscott, piano.
      On container: Taped for KUSC FM use only, c/o Glen Slaton.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 March 29 (Box 72)
      On container: "Black Arthur - Black Musician," Volume 1, Part II.
    - Highlights - Past Concerts of U.G.M.A.A./Pan Afrikan People's Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), 1972 March 29 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Ballad for Samuel (Widney, 1971 July 19) -- African Village (The Gathering, 1972 March 5) -- The Grip (Bing Concert, 1970 July 20) -- The Giant (Bing Concert, 1970 July 20) -- Inspirations of Silence -- Dark Tree -- Warriors All -- J.O.B. -- St. Michael.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 4 (Box 72)
      Horace Tapscott, instructor; with Linda Hill.
    - The Black Experience, Fine Arts at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Morning in Riverside -- Blues.
      Black Arthur Trio Personnel: Black Arthur, alto saxophone; Roberto Miranda, bass; John Blue, percussion.
    - The Black Experience, Fine Arts at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Blues (pt. II).
      peronnel: the Black Arthur Trio.
    - The Black Experience, Fine Arts at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Little A's Chant / Herbert K. Baker -- Lush Life / Billy Strayhorn.
      On container: Master Copy - 1972 ,Dup Part II.
    - The Black Experience in the Fine Arts at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 11 (Box 72)
      Subject: The Life of Herbert Baker. Instructor: Horace Tapscott.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), #1, 1972 April 11 (Box 72)
      "The Life and the Music of Herbert Keith Baker."
      Horace Tapscott, instructor.
    - The Black Experience, at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), #1, 1972 April 11 (Box 72)
    - The Black Experience in the Fine Arts at the University of California at Riverside (U.C.R.), 1972 April 13 (Box 72)
      Program: Herbert Baker, Black Musician. Speakers: Mr. and Mrs. James Ortis Baker (Herbie's parents).
    - Black Experience in the Fine Arts at Riverside, 1972 April 18 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Seize the Time -- Horace.. -- In the Bottoms Suite -- Black Woman -- Conversation and Thoughts
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney, 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: Sketches of Drunken Mary / Horace Tapscott -- The Creator Has A Master Plan / Pharoah Sanders -- Sunrise, Sunset.
      Personnel includes: Black Arthur, Will Connell, alto saxophone; Linda Hill, vocals; Horace Tapscott, piano; David Bryant, bass; Everett Brown, Jr., percussion.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      Compositions include: In A Sentimental Mood / Duke Ellington -- Niger's Theme / H. Tapscott.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), in concert at Widney High School, 1972 April 6 (Box 72)
      On container: Master copy.
    - Black Experience Nate Morgan, 1972 April 18 (Box 72)
    - Black Experience in Fine Arts, 1972 April 20 (Box 72)
      Program: Nate Morgan, Black Musician. Personnel: Nate Morgan, piano -- Richard Herrera, bass -- Cornell Fauler, drums.
    - Children's Stories Series, Volume I, Part I, 1972 April 20 (Box 72)
      Compositions: Llemah's Light -- Soul of Music.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney H.S., Part 3, Oscar Brown Sextet, 1972 April 23 (Box 70)
      Compositions: The Beginning (continued) -- Black Woman / Luther Keyes, poet.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney H.S., Part 4, Will Cornell, Jr. Sextet, 1972 April 23 (Box 70)
      Compositions: Deon / Lor. Garman -- Will Tune (Theme) / W.C., Jr. -- Moon In Leo / Nate Morgan.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney H.S., Part 5, 1972 April 23 (Box 70)
      Compositions: Moon In Leo (continued) / Nate Morgan -- Black National Anthem, Lift Every Voice.
    - Pan Afrikan Peoples Arkestra (P.A.P.A.), at Widney H.S., Part 1, 1972 April 23 (Box 70)
      Compositions: Calvary / Negro Spiritual -- The Creator Has A Master Plan / Pharoah Sanders and Leon Thomas -- Faithia / Will Connell, Jr. -- African Village / McCoy Tyner